{
    "id": "a4fefcfabd704482904fb8aacaa95204",
    "title": "Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She …………….. school at fourteen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "was leaving",
                "has left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. his letter a week ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was receiving",
                "have received",
                "received",
                "had received"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When I saw him, he ……………… chess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was playing",
                "played",
                "has been playing",
                "is playing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The guests ………………… before he reached home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "had gone",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The train had left before I ……………… the station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have reached",
                "reached",
                "was reaching",
                "had reached"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………… in the garage when John turned up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "have been working",
                "was working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When I opened the door, the cat ………………. out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "jumped",
                "was jumping",
                "has jumped"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. when the lights went out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "was reading",
                "have been reading"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His father ………………. last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "was dying",
                "has died"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Babar ………………. Rana Sanga in the battle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "defeated",
                "was defeating",
                "has defeated"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}